In the left hand side, here we have
在左侧 我们看到
the Filepicker where all of our files will be located.
文件定位栏  用于显示我们的文件位置
We can add new files by clicking this.
我们可以点击这里 添加新的文件
We create new folders by clicking this button right here.
点击这里的按钮 创建新的文件夹
Rename the folder and then create it right there.
在这里为文件夹重命名 并点击 创建文件夹 即可
Then we have our files here so we can open our file,
然后 文件会显示在这边 我们可以打开文件
and then up here along the top,
也可以点击顶部这里
we can close it here.
关闭文件
If we need to upload new files or directories,
如果我们想要上传新的文件或名录
we can come down here and we could just drag and drop them onto here
我们可以点击这里 将文件拖到这 并进行上传
or just click on this and it will give us the pop-up window.
或者 点击这里 会出现弹出窗口
Now to open up a new terminal, we can come down here.
如果想要打开一个新的终端 我们可以点击这里
And if this is your first terminal,
如果这是你第一次建终端
you can just click on NEW TERMINAL and then after that,
你可以直接点击屏幕显示的 NEW TERMINAL（新终端）
any subsequent windows we need to open,
如果我们之后需要打开新的窗口
that we can just do with the little plus sign here.
就可以直接点击这里的 “+” 符号
Just keep clicking that and you'll open up a lot of new terminal windows.
一直点击 你可以打开许多新的终端窗口
And then we can just keep closing them all along.
我们也可以点击关闭这些窗口
So this is a terminal so you can install
这就是终端 你可以在这里安装
any dependencies or install any packages with it.
任意依赖项 或安装任何包
One thing to note about this though is that this starts out in home/workspace,
有一点要注意 这是以 home/workspace 开始
which is the same location as over here, home/workspace.
和这里显示的位置 home/workspace 是一样的
So if we come over here and we list these files,
如果我们在这里 列举这些文件
these files here are the ones you're seeing over here.
这些文件就是你在这里看到的
So when you add new files or upload new files,
如果你新建文件或上传新文件
that goes into home workspace which is what your terminal starts out in.
它会在 home workspace 显示  也会显示在你的终端这里
Once you started developing on your project and you're ready to see it in the browser,
当你开始创建项目时 你会在浏览程序中看到它
you come down over here and click OPEN PREVIEW TAB. Let's do that now.
你可以点击下方的 OPEN PREVIEW TAB （打开预览标签） 我们来试试
Now, this is the URL for this specific project.
现在可以看到 这个特定项目的 URL
Yours will definitely be different.
你自己项目的 URL 肯定不同
And notice that this project is not running any server,
注意 这个项目还没有运行任何服务器
so nothing is actually running,
所以目前没有程序在运行
so we're not actually seeing anything.
我们也看不到任何东西
If you get this, make sure you're actually running
如果你到达这一步 请确保你的确在运行服务器
a server or create React app that actually something is running.
或者创建了一个实际在运行的 React 应用
Let's go check out how to do that.
我们来看看怎么做
Now that we've stalled everything,
现在 一切已经安装好
I can start the server.
我可以启动服务器
Now the project is running but again,
现在 项目在运行 但是请注意
don't open up local host.
不要打开本地主机
We need to click on OPEN PREVIEW TAB.
我们需要点击 OPEN PREVIEW TAB （打开预览标签）
And here is our project.
现在能看到我们的项目
Once you've finished your project,
当你完成项目后
you come over here and click SUBMIT PROJECT.
你可以点击这里 SUBMIT PROJECT （提交项目）
This will send it off to be reviewed.
项目就会被提交 被审阅
And then the last thing to point out is this menu button.
最后需要注意的一点是 菜单按钮
If something's going kind of crazy with your workspace,
如果你的工作区中出现问题
just click on REFRESH WORKSPACE and that will
只要点击 REFRESH WORKSPACE （刷新工作区）
build you out a new workspace but will keep all of your data.
这样你会新建一个工作区 并在那里保存你所有的数据
If you want to start over from scratch and erase all of your work and all of your files, 00:02:16,900 --&gt; 00:00:00,000 just click on RESET DATA down here and that will erase everything and start from scratch.
如果你想要从头开始 清除掉之前的内容和所有的文件 00:02:16,900 --&gt; 00:00:00,000 直接点击 RESET DATA （重置数据） 就会清除一切内容 让你从头开始